

# Summary

+3 years of experience of using a combination of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build everything a user sees and interacts with on a website—that includes everything from front-end features like fonts, sliders, drop-down menus, and buttons, to the overall manner in which web content like photos, videos, and articles are displayed in your web browser.

## **Education**

2008-09 -2012-07

#### **HICMIS**

The high institute for computer & management information system

## 🔉 Ce

#### **Certificates**

2014-04

Web design course

### **Experience**

2015-01 -2016-12

### Junior UI developer

Arabia inform

I started my work at arabia inform company as a UI web developer for one year.

2016-01 present

#### Front end developer

Media pan arab

I went to media pan arab company as a front end developer and still here for now.



## Work projects

2016-02 -2016-06

#### Euro korabia

http://euro.korabia.com

This is football website news about euro championship news and we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript] in this project.

2016-07 -2016-09

#### Can korabia

http://can.korabia.com

This is football website news about can championship news and we used **[html, scss, jquery, javascript]** in this project.

2016-10 -

#### Shamlola

2017-01 http://www.shamlola.com/

This project is for cooking recopies and contain some of good books for cooking and we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript] in this project.

2017-02 -2017-05

#### So3ody play

https://play.so3ody.com

This project is a game about football matches and competition and



## **Personal Info**

#### Phone

+201126199254

#### E-mail

ahmed.farag305@gmail.com

#### Date of birth

1991-09-09

#### GitHub

github.com/ahmedfarag2010

#### Facebook

facebook.com/ahmed.faraq.dev

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/ahmed-faraga22a1a117/



#### Skills

HTML,HTML5

Css,Css3

Bootstrap 3/4

Pug

SCSS

Javascript

JQuery

Gulp.js

Ajax

Webpack

Angular 2/4/5/6

••••

challenge between players and we used **[html, scss, jquery, javascript]** in this project.

#### 2017-01 -

#### Pec

2017-03

http://pec-co.net/
This project is for choose/select trainer/player some of sport games and i

used [html, scss, jquery, javascript] in this project.

#### 2017-06 -

#### Korabreak

2017-09

http://www.korabreak.com/

This project is for mix of football news and contain some videos and we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript] in this project.

#### 2017-10 -

### World cup

2018-01

http://worldcup.korabia.com/

This project is for worldcup championship news and we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript, gulp.js] in this project.

#### 2018-03 -

#### New shamlola

2018-05

http://new.shamlola.com/

This project is for cooking recopies and contain some of good books for cooking and we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript] in this project.

#### 2018-04 -

### So3ody

2018-05

http://www.so3ody.com/

This project is for football news around asia continental and the arabic world and we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript, gulp.js, webpack, vue.js, ajax] in this project.

## 2018-06 -

### New so3ody

present

http://testnew.so3ody.com/

This project is a newer copy of last project we used [html, scss, jquery, javascript, gulp.js, webpack, ajax] in this project.